xforce-cracks.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy Policy | xForceCracks

## What personal data we collect, and why?

We collect information to provide you with the services you have subscribed to, and to personalize and improve your experience using our services.

All this information is stored on secure servers.

We only use personal data that you have given us or collected during your visit to our site or our purchase orders. We do not collect personal information or sell it to external partners. We may share your information with partners but only to provide you with the publication to which you have subscribed or to improve your user experience on the site. We never share your personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes.

The personal information about you that we collect generally falls into 2 categories:

  * __The information you provide__

We may ask you to provide us with personal information to provide you with the service you expect. We may ask you for your contact information to provide you with your publication or to create an account to access the reserved parts of the site. We may also ask you to enter your payment information so that you can pay for your purchases, and also offer to back them up to facilitate your subsequent orders.

The personal data we ask you to provide, and the reason we ask for it, are clearly indicated at collection points.

  * __The information we collect automatically__

When you visit our site or our purchase orders, we may automatically collect certain information from your device. The data we collect may include information such as your ip address, device type, unique identification number, browser type, and other technical information. We may also collect information about how your device interacted with our site or purchase orders, including the list of pages you accessed and links you clicked on. We collect this information in order to better understand the visitors who visit our website and who look at our order forms, and to identify the content that interests them the most. The use of this information allows us to improve the quality and relevance of our website and services. Some of this information may be collected through the use of cookies and other similar technologies. You will find more information in our [Cookie Usage Policy](http://www.xforce-cracks.com/cookies-policy/)

## Who do we share your personal information with?

We may share your information with the following categories of recipients:

  * The Support Companies that provide us with the main services of data processing, such as ensuring the security of our site, and processing data for the purposes described above, or that were presented to you when we collected your data. Publishing Factory (based in Lausanne, Switzerland) provides us with most data processing services, including hosting and storing our database on their servers.
  * Trusted Third-Party Companies that provide additional data processing services, analyze data, provide marketing services, and manage credit card processing. These third parties have only limited access to the data they need when performing their services, and can not use them for any other purpose. In addition, they have a contractual obligation to use them in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.
  * Legal or similar bodies, since we believe that the transmission of information is necessary (i) in case of legal obligation or (ii) to establish and defend our legitimate rights, and
  * Any other person you have designated, with your express agreement.

## How do we guarantee the protection of your Personal Data?

We have taken the appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect the data we collect and process. These measures are intended to provide the level of security needed to respond to the risks associated with processing your data. When we share the data with Third Party companies, we ensure that the data will also be protected, and will not be provided or resold to an unauthorized third party.

## International data transfers

Your personal information may be transferred and processed in countries other than the country in which you are resident. These countries may have data protection laws different from those of your country (and, in some cases, may not be as protective). In particular, some of the recipients of personal data that we collect are located outside the European Union, including the United States. For example, the data you provide to us as a Customer is collected and processed on our behalf by Publishing Factory SA, based in Lausanne – Switzerland, and some servers based in Baltimore, USA. The United States does not currently have a uniform law on data protection,

## Data retention

We retain the personal information we collect from you when we have a legitimate business interest in doing so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested) or to comply with legal, tax or accounting requirements. When we no longer have a legitimate interest in justifying the processing of your personal information, we delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup), we store your data securely.

## Legal basis for the processing of personal data.

The legal basis for collecting and using personal data as described above depends on the type of information and the setting in which we collected it.

We collect your personal information in the following cases:

  * The information is necessary to fill a service (for example, we need your email address to send you a newsletter, and your postal address to deliver your order);
  * The treatment we do is necessary to defend one of our legitimate interests, without exceeding your own rights.
  * You have explicitly consented (for example, you have checked a box that allows us to send you advertising for products or services of partners, which we think may be of interest to you); or
  * The information is necessary to fulfill our legal obligations (tax obligations for example)

We finance our free newsletter through advertising. There may be one or more small advertising inserts inserted in our messages, as well as messages dedicated to the promotion of certain offers. By subscribing to our newsletter, you agree to receive these promotional messages (we can not remove advertising inserts from our messages).

Each of our messages has an unsubscribe link that you can use to unsubscribe at any time.

When we collect and use your personal data on the basis of our legitimate interest, it will be to enable us to provide or improve our services, sites and communications, namely prospecting and direct marketing actions, fraud prevention , the management of the questions of customers and prospects … We may have to rely on the legitimate interest for other treatments and, if necessary, we will tell you when necessary what are these legitimate interests.

## Your rights in the protection of personal data

You have the following rights regarding the protection of personal data:

  * If you wish to access, correct, update or request the deletion of your personal information, you may do so at any time by contacting us using the contact details provided under “How to contact us”. We may not be entitled to delete your personal information if we are required to retain it in order to comply with our legal obligations, perform a public interest mission, establish, exercise or defend any legal claim or claim. exercise our right to freedom of expression and information.
  * In addition, you may object to the processing of your personal information, ask us to limit the processing of your personal information or request the portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact information provided in the “How to contact us” section.
  * You have the right to refuse marketing communications that we send to you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the promotional emails we send you. To opt out of other forms of marketing (such as mail marketing or telemarketing), please contact us using the contact information provided in the “How to Contact Us” section below.
  * If we have collected and processed your personal data with your consent, you may withdraw your consent at any time. The withdrawal of your consent will not affect the legality of any treatment we have performed prior to your withdrawal, nor the processing of your personal information made on the basis of legal grounds of treatment other than consent.
  * You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact the Commission Nationale Informatique et Libertés (CNIL). We are committed to responding to any inquiries regarding your data protection rights in accordance with applicable laws.

## Updates to this privacy policy

Please note that this privacy policy may be amended or supplemented at any time, in particular to comply with any legislative, regulatory, jurisprudential or technological developments. In such a case, the date of its update will be clearly identified at the top of this policy and we will take appropriate steps to inform you, in accordance with the importance of the changes we will make. We will obtain your consent to any significant privacy policy changes if and on the points required by applicable data protection laws.

## How to contact us ?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the use of your personal information, please contact us by sending an email to personal-data@xforce-cracks.com
